titlesApp
 .constant('FAQ', [
   {
     question: 'Question 1: What does “crowd-translation” mean in this project? 項目“眾包翻譯”是什麼意思',
     answer: 'Answer: Crowd-translation allows Ming scholars around the world to contribute English translations of Ming official titles that have not yet been translated by Charles Hucker in A Dictionary of Official Titles in Imperial China. These scholars may also review and comment on translations submitted by their peers whose identities will remain anonymous. 意在邀請全球明代研究專家學者對明代官名進行翻譯，尤其是未被賀凱（Charles O. Hucker）在《中國古代官名辭典》（A Dictionary of Official Titles in Imperial China）裡收錄翻譯過的官名。並通過匿名方式審閱評論其他專家遞交的英文翻譯'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 2: What is the time frame during which I can make contributions through the crowd-translation system? 我能通過該系統參與眾包翻譯的時間段是什麼？',
     answer: 'Answer: The crowd-translation system will be open from November 7th, 2016 through July 6th, 2017.  眾包翻譯系統將在2016年11月7日至2017年7月6日期間運行。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 3: What can we expect from the crowd-translation project?  項目的最終成果和用途是什麼？',
     answer: 'Answer:  There will be mainly two products of the project: “A Bilingual Dictionary of Ming Government Official Titles” (e-book) and a reusable computer source code package for similar translation projects. Both will be made freely available to the public (open-access) by the end of September 2017, the e-book at <a href="http://escholarship.org/">e-Scholarship</a>, the University of California’s institutional repository; the source code at <a href="https://github.com/">GitHub</a>, a significant site for system developers to develop and share their computer source codes. The dictionary will also be used to improve the <a href="http://projects.iq.harvard.edu/cbdb/home">China Biographical Database (CBDB)</a>. 本項目最終將出版優化完善的網絡免費版中英雙語《明代官名辭典》。該辭典計畫在2017年9月底於加州大學的 <a href="http://escholarship.org/">e-Scholarship</a>上開放使用，同時也為<a href="http://projects.iq.harvard.edu/chinesecbdb">中國人物傳記資料庫</a>的完善提供必要的工具。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 4: When multiple translations are submitted, who decides which is the best translation for the dictionary? 最終官名翻譯由誰來決定？',
     answer: 'Answer: A group of three Ming scholar consultants will make the final decisions, based upon their knowledge and comments and justifications from contributors. 由三位明代研究學者組成的專家小組將會對最終選入中英雙語《明代官名辭典》的英文譯名進行評審裁奪。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 5: Where do the official titles in the system come from? Why are there some unofficial titles?系統官名的主要來源是什麼？為什麼系統中會出現一些非正式官名？',
     answer: 'Answer: Ming government official titles currently in the system come from two sources: automatic text mining of historical documents in Academica Sinica’s databases, which is done by the <a href="http://projects.iq.harvard.edu/cbdb/home">China Biographical Database (CBDB)</a> group, and manual extraction by the project team from other primary sources, such as Ming Shi and Da Ming Hui Dian. Some unofficial titles are included as part of automatic text mining results. 本系統的官名主要有兩個來源：一是中國人物傳記資料庫（CBDB）團隊對中央研究院數據庫資料進行文本挖掘，二是項目小組依據《明史》、《大明會典》進行人工提取。因為本項目也旨在為中國人物傳記資料庫（CBDB）提供必要的工具，所以CBDB文本挖掘來的非正式官名也被收入以尋求眾包翻譯。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 6: How are official titles organized in the system? Why isn’t the classification scheme of Ming Shi used? 系統中的官名是按照什麼原則進行排序的？為什麼沒有按照明史的分類方式進行排序？',
     answer: 'Answer: Official titles in the system are first sorted in an ascending order of the number of translations received, and then by the descending position of their affiliated institutions in the system. 官名首先按照所收到的英譯名數量由低至高排序，數量相等的情況下，按照官名所屬機構位置進行排序。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 7: How can one participate in this project? 如何才能參與這個項目？',
     answer: 'Answer: Scholars of Ming studies or dynastic political systems may sign up to participate. Signing-up is very simple, requiring only one’s name, country of residence and email address, primarily for administrative purposes. After one’s registration is approved, s/he may log in and contribute. One’s name and country of residence will appear on the Contributors page after making at least one submission. 明代研究和中國古代近代政治制度史專家和學者都歡迎參與，您只需稍作基本信息（姓名、所在國家和電子郵件地址）登記就可以參與這個項目了。填入的基本信息中除了姓名和所在國家會在遞交英文翻譯或評論後在Contributors頁面的項目貢獻者名單中出現，其它只是在後台由項目小組成員妥善保管、酌情使用。個人基本信息的添寫也有助於眾包翻譯的質量控制。具體參與項目貢獻英譯官名等則需要先用您註冊時建立的帳號和密碼進行登錄。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 8: What specific contributions may I make to the project? 我具體可為項目做哪些工作？',
     answer: 'Answer: One may review and comment on Chinese Title, Pinyin Title and English Title already in the system, besides adding new English translations. One may also send suggestions to us about other potential scholar contributors or missing official titles from the system. Translation and comment submissions will be displayed on each contributor’s Profile page. 您一方面可以對系統現存的中文官名、拼音注音、英文翻譯進行評論；另一方面可以增加新的英文翻譯，您也可推薦該領域專家幫助翻譯或提交尚未被收入系統的官名。您所做的翻譯和評論工作可以在 Profile中看到。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 9: How do I find official title that  I’m interested in?如何以最快方式找到我感興趣的官名？',
     answer: 'Answer: For official titles of interest, one may search by Chinese title or pinyin title, or browse by affiliated institutions on the left side of the main page. 系統提供兩種檢索入口，其一是通過漢語官名（Chinese Title）或拼音官名（Pinyin Title）檢索，其二是通過主頁左側的三級官名分類表瀏覽，在相應類目下找到所需官名。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 10: May I delete or edit other scholars’ translations?我可以直接刪除或修改他人翻譯的內容嗎？',
     answer: 'Answer: No. contributors may only delete or edit their own submissions. But they may comment on translations submitted by others. 不可以。只能對本人翻譯的內容進行刪除或修改，對其他作者翻譯內容，可以評論，但不能刪除和編輯。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 11: Will my contributions be acknowledged? And how? 本人的參與和貢獻將如何被認證？',
     answer: 'Answer: Ming scholar participants who make at least one submission to the crowd-translation system will have their names displayed in alphabetical order by last names on the Contributors page in the system. All contributors’ names will be also acknowledged in the forthcoming Bilingual Dictionary of Ming Government Official Titles. 在“Contributors”頁面上，將會按姓氏順序列出所有使用本系統參與明代官名翻譯的專家學者，同時，貢獻者名單也會出現在將要出版的雙語《明代官名辭典》里。'
   },
   {
     question: 'Question 12: How may I provide general suggestions and comments, or make specific suggestions on additional Ming official titles and potential scholar contributors? 如何對除了已收入系統的明官名以外的項目部份提出改進意見？',
     answer: 'Answer: One may log in and click on the Contact Us link.  The project team will respond to all email messages. 歡迎登錄後在“Contact Us”頁面向項目小組提出增加具體意見和建議，項目小組將及時跟進并與您討論。'
   },
 ]);
